friendlane.com 2010-08-10

# Privacy Policy-Friendlane.com

_FriendLane.Com respects the privacy of the visitors to its Sites_

"Personal Information" is information about you that is personally identifiable to you, like your name, address, email address, or phone number, as well as other non-public information that is associated with the foregoing.   
"Anonymous Information" means information that is not associated with or linked to your Personal Information; Anonymous Information does not permit the identification of individual persons. We collect and use Personal Information and Anonymous Information as described in this Privacy Policy. 

_User Consent_

By submitting Personal Information through our Sites, you agree to the terms of this Privacy Policy and expressly consent to the processing of your Personal Information according to this Privacy Policy.

 _General_

We collect Personal Information that you submit to us voluntarily through our Sites.  
When you register for the FriendLane.Com services, we will collect your name, email address, your gender, date of birth and ZIP code.  
When you save other Personal Information in your profile we will collect any such information you enter.  
When you enter Personal Information throughout the FriendLane.Com network using one of the features of the FriendLane.Com network, for example journals, testimonials, groups, or message boards, we will collect any such information you enter ("Publicly Posted Information").  
When you contact us by sending us an email, we will collect your email addresses and any information contained in the email you send us.

Once you register with FriendLane.Com and sign in to our Services, you are not anonymous to us. If you are browsing the Sites without registering with FriendLane.Com, you are anonymous to us, but we will collect the information listed below under Personal Information Collected Via Technology.   
If you choose to use our invitation service to tell a friend about our site, we will ask you for information needed to send the invitation, such as your friend's email address. We will send your friend an email inviting him or her to visit the site. 

_Use of information_

Any visitor of the Sites can view your profile information and photos that you have uploaded to the FriendLane.Com community. To provide you with some of the features that the FriendLane.Com community offers to its members, we may use Personal Information that is stored in your profile after you have requested such features, for example to send invitation emails to people that you specified as being interested in joining the FriendLane.Com community. Please be aware that any information that is publicly posted throughout the FriendLane.Com network can be accessed by every visitor of the Sites. FriendLane.Com may analyze any collected information for its own internal purposes. In addition, FriendLane.Com may remove personally identifying information from collected information to render it anonymous. FriendLane.Com may use Anonymous Information for any purpose and disclose Anonymous Information in its discretion.

 _Information Sharing and Disclosure_

FriendLane.Com does not rent, sell, or share personal information about you with other people or nonaffiliated companies except to provide products or services you've requested, when we have your permission, or as otherwise described in this privacy policy.  
We provide your Personal Information to third party service providers who work on behalf of or with FriendLane.Com under confidentiality agreements to provide some of the services and features of the FriendLane.Com community and to help us communicate with FriendLane.Com Members. These service providers may use your personal information to communicate with you about offers and services from FriendLane.Com and our marketing partners. However, these service providers do not have any independent right to share this information.  
We will disclose information in response to subpoenas, court orders, or legal process, or to establish or exercise our legal rights or defend against legal claims. We may disclose information, if we believe it is necessary to investigate, prevent, or take action regarding suspected illegal activities or fraud, situations involving the physical safety of any person, violations of FriendLane.Com's terms of use, or as otherwise required by applicable law.  
If assets are acquired by another company, that company will possess the Personal Information collected by us and it will assume the rights and obligations regarding your Personal Information as described in this Privacy Policy.

 _Personal Information Collected Via Technology_

As you navigate the Sites, certain information may also be passively collected and stored on our server logs, including your Internet protocol address, browser type, and operating system. We also use Cookies and navigational data like Uniform Resource Locators (URL) to gather information regarding the date and time of your visit and the solutions and information for which you searched and viewed, or on which of the advertisements displayed on the Sites you clicked. This type of information is collected to make our Services and solutions more useful to you and to tailor the FriendLane.Com community experience to meet your special interests and needs.If you search the FriendLane.Com community by using a toolbar that FriendLane.Com, or a third party provides, we may collect Anonymous Information about you automatically, but we will not collect Personal Information. 

An "Internet protocol address" or "IP Address" is a number that is automatically assigned to your computer when you use the Internet. In some cases your IP Address stays the same from browser session to browser session; but if you use a consumer internet access provider, your IP Address probably varies from session to session. We track your IP Address when you login to the Sites.

"Cookies" are small pieces of information that a web site sends to your computer's hard drive while you are viewing a web site. FriendLane.Com may use both session Cookies (which expire once you close your web browser) and persistent Cookies (which stay on your computer until you delete them) to provide you with a more personal and interactive experience on the Sites. Persistent Cookies can be removed by following your Internet browser help file directions. If you choose to disable Cookies, some areas of the Sites may not work properly.  
Other third parties may place advertisements and cookies on webpages within the FriendLane.Com network. Other companies' use of their cookies is subject to their own privacy policies, not this one.

 _Confidentiality and Security_

We limit access to personal information about you to employees and third parties who we reasonably believe need access to that information to provide products or services to you or in order to do their jobs. We have physical, electronic, and procedural safeguards to protect personal information about you and your FriendLane.Com account information is protected by a password that you select. FriendLane.Com uses industry-standard SSL encryption in certain areas of the Sites to protect data transmissions. However, no company, including FriendLane.Com, can fully eliminate security risks associated with Personal Information.

 _Other Sites_

Our provision of a link to any other Sites or location is for your convenience and does not signify our endorsement of such other Sites or location or its contents. We have no control over, do not review, and cannot be responsible for these outside Sites or their content. Please be aware that the terms of our Privacy Policy does not apply to these outside Sites.

 _Regarding Children_

We do not intentionally gather Personal Information about visitors who are under the age of 13.

 _Privacy Policy Update_

FriendLane have the right to update this policy from time to time. We will notify you about significant changes in the way we treat Personal Information by sending a notice to the primary email address specified in your FriendLane.Com account or by placing a prominent notice on our Sites. If you object to any such changes, you must cease using our Sites. Continued use of our Sites following notice of any such changes shall indicate your acknowledgement of such changes and agreement to be bound by the terms and conditions of such changes.
